Blake Sim

20, Hagui-ro, Dongan-gu, Anyang-si, 14044 | 82-10-5715-9729 | nbblks@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Highly motivated frontend developer seeking an opportunity to work in a collaborative team environment with 3 years of strong experience that covers frontend and backend technologies. The main technical stacks are JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML/CSS, React.js, and aspired to deliver high-quality web applications.

EXPERIENCE

Neulpeummaru - Frontend Developer

SEOUL

Neulpeummaru CRM (TypeScript, React, Zustand, SWR, TailwindCSS)

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

- Managed Nuelpummaru CRM web app for order and stock sync, improving code efficiency and maintainability.
- Implemented extensive code refactoring, reducing component size for enhanced readability and development efficiency.
- Enhanced code quality with linter, formatter, and optimized global state management, fostering efficient cross-functional communication between diverse teams.

Noleeui Balgyeon - Frontend Developer

SEOUL

Noleeui Balgyeon Web (TypeScript, React, Redux, Styled-Components, Redux-toolkit)

- Maintained legacy booking system, resolved web service issues resulting in enhanced platform stability.
- Integrated Airbridge BI solution, managed 20+ event points for marketers to track user data, enhancing analytics capabilities.
- Revamped color theme for web and web view resulting in a more visually appealing and consistent user interface.

Blockchain Labs - Frontend Developer

SEOUL

BlockChat Admin (TypeScript, React, Emotion.js, Google Analytics 4)

Feb 2022 - Feb 2023

Apr 2023 - July 2023

- Orchestrated planning and implementation of admin web app prototype and coordinated with backend developers.
- Developed company homepage and landing pages, optimizing for SEO and implementing UTM parameters for tracking.
- Achieved a unified product look with a new design UI kit and improved web performance by 50% through asset reduction and component reusability.

SDPlex - Full Stack Web Developer

SEOUL

OnCue Admin (Java, SpringBoot, Thymeleaf, PostgreSQL, SQLite)

Apr 2019- Apr 2020

- Designed and developed OnCue Admin, a dynamic web dashboard for monitoring resource usage and settings.
- Managed real-time data, implementing optimal structures for interactive charts across industry modules.
- Integrated long polling for real-time panel updates, providing a comprehensive view of OnCue Servers' resources.

EDUCATION

KOREA NATIONAL OPEN UNIVERSITY

Seoul

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Computer Science (Feb 2022)

- **GPA:** 4.1
- Relevant Coursework: Data Structure, Operating Systems, Computer Networks, Database Systems
- Awards & Honors: Honor Award (2021)

KYUNGHEE UNIVERSITY

Seoul

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Journalism and Communication (Feb 2018)

- **GPA:** 3.5
- Awards & Honors: Honor Award (2015)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML/CSS
- Frameworks and Libraries: React.js, Next.js, Redux.js, Recoil.js, Emotion.js, TailwindCSS,
- Database: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Cloud Firestore, SQLite
- Testing: Jest, react-testing-library, Cypress
- Infrastructure: AWS(EC2, S3, Cloudfront), CI/CD(Docker, Jenkins, Github Actions)
- Tools: Git, Jira, Figma

CERTIFICATES

• Amazon Web Services - AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (June 2021)